Do you feel lucky?
Hostel: Part III is a horror film directed by Scott Spiegel.
Set in Las Vegas, the film centers on a man who attends his best friend's bachelor
party, unaware of an insidious agenda that plays into hunting humans.
Carter McMullen, played by Kip Pardue.
Scott, played by Brian Hallisay.
Justin, played by John Hensley.
Kendra, played by Sarah Habel.
Travis, played by Chris Coy.
Mike Malloy, played by Skyler Stone.
Hostel: Part III is a 2011 American horror film directed by Scott
Spiegel and the final installment in the Hostel film series.
It was written by Michael D.
This is the only film in the series to not have Eli Roth involved in the
production and is also the only one not to have a theatrical release.
The film also relocates the Elite Hunting Club from Slovakia to Las Vegas.
The plot centers on four men attending a bachelor party in Las Vegas.
While there, they are enticed by two prostitutes to join
them at a private party way off the Strip.
Once there, they are horrified to find themselves the subjects of a perverse game of torture,
where members of the Elite Hunting Club are hosting the most sadistic show in town.
It was released direct-to-DVD on December 27, 2011.
This was Spiegel’s last film he directed before his death in 2025.
The film explores themes of sadism, sequel, torture, las vegas, torture porn.
The tone is dark.